susan mayer had always believed the one good thing about hard times
Susan Mayer一直认为 困境唯一的好处
is that you get to find out who your friends really are.
就是能让你发现谁才是真正的朋友
When her grandmother died, it was bree who brought homemade cookies.
当她祖母去世的时候 是Bree带来的亲手做的饼干
When the critics panned her third book,
当批评家大肆否定她的第三本书
it was gabrielle who hired the handsome masseur.
是Gabrielle请了帅气的按摩师
When her divorce became final, it was lynette who poured the scotch.
当她离婚的时候 是Lynette陪她喝酒
Sadly, susan's life had been shattered once again...
很不幸，Susan的生活又一次遭遇困境
but as always, her friends had come to help pick up the pieces.
但是她的朋友一如既往 都来帮她收拾残局了
Susan?We've all been talking. We've decided you and julie should stay with bree.
Susan，我们一直在讨论 我们决定你和Julie和Bree住一起
Oh, thanks. No, that's okay. We'll stay at a motel.
谢谢，不过不用了 我们去住旅馆吧
Absolutely not.
千万别去
Just give me an hour or two to straighten up andrew's room, and then you can bringyour...
给我一个小时收拾一下Andrew的房间 然后你们就可以带着你们的...
selves over.
你们自己过来了
I don't deserve friends like you.
有你们这样的朋友我三生有幸
We're aware of that.
我们也知道
susan, you're running lowon trash bags. I'm going to run to the store.
Susan，你的垃圾袋快用完了 我去一趟商店
Thanks, orson.Thanks for coming.
谢谢你,Orson,谢谢你能来
You know,you didn't have to do this.
你知道你不必这样做的
Hey, it's my pleasure.
我乐意啊
Mrs. Mayer!
Mayer太太！
Hi. Bud penrod,town and country insurance the "can-do" people.
你好，我是Bud Penrod城市保险公司的 是“能帮忙”的人
Oh, it's nice to meet you.
很高兴见到你
Yeah. Look at that.
看看这里
Well, that's no fun at all,is it?
一点也不好笑对吧
No. No, it isn'T.
对，对，一点也不
So when am I gonna getthe check?
我什么时候能拿到赔款呢？
'Cause I have a lot of rebuilding to do. I need to get started.
有很多地方都要重建 我要马上开始做了
Yeah, well, I'm afraidthat's going to be a while.
对，可是，恐怕还要一段时间
You see, the fire department has ruled that this was arson.
消防部门认为有人故意纵火
Arson?
故意纵火？
Yeah. So we can't give youany money until we finish our investigation.
嗯，所以在我们调查完之前 我们不能支付赔款
Who would wanna burn down my house?
谁会放火烧我的房子？
I don't know.Do you have any enemies?
我不知道，你有什么冤家对头吗？
No. No, look it.The whole neighborhood turned out to help.
没有啊，你看，周围的人家都来帮忙了
I'm very popular.
我很受欢迎的
And there's no one among them that wishes you ill?
没有人和你不对吗？
Oh, no, no.Everybody's been very helpful.
没有，大家都很帮忙
Um, everybody likes me.Absolutely...
所有人都喜欢我，绝对...
everyone.
每个人都喜欢
Yes, hard times were what susan used to distinguish who was a friend and who wasn't.
是的 Susan用困境来判断谁是朋友谁是敌人
The Desperate Housewives Season 02  Episode 22 NO ONE IS ALONE
绝望的主妇 第2季 第22集 无人孤单
Not everyone enjoys being a small part of a large community.
不是所有的人 都愿意成为一个大社区的一部分
Indeed, some yearn to leave the stress and noise of constant companionship behind them
事实上，一些人渴望离开 来自同伴的压力和喧嚣
so they strike out  on their own,
开始单独行动
hoping their solitude will bring a little peace and quiet.
希望独处能带来平静与安宁
It's only then they discover how dangerous it is...
直到那时他们才发现
to be alone in the world.
独自一人是多么危险
zach, did you get the trash?
Zach,你倒垃圾了吗？
How'd you get in here?
你怎么进来的？
Hiya, paul.
你好，Paul
I stood at the back door shouting and shouting. Were you in the little boys room?
我在你后门使劲喊你 你是在孩子的房间里吗？
I'm calling the police.
我要报警了
No need. I just needed to borrow some flour.
不用，我就是要借一些面粉
I'm a little bit psychic,and I predict fresh-baked cookies in your future.
我可以通灵哦 我可以预见你有新鲜的饼干吃
Zachary.
Zachary
What'd she want?
她想干什么？
She was in the cupboard.
她开了橱柜
Get a trash bag.We're throwing everything away.
拿个垃圾袋来 我们要把东西都扔掉
You think she was trying to poison us?
你觉得她给我们下了毒？
All I know is we're eating out tonight.
不管怎样我们今晚要在外面吃饭了
What do you want?
你想干嘛？
this is a little awkward, and I apologize in advance for how this is gonna sound,but
不好意思哦 我提前为我要说的话道歉 但是，
um...by any chance,did... you burn down my house?
你是不是...是不是 烧了我的房子？
Yes.
没错
What?
什么？
Yes, I burnt down your house,you sleazy little whore.
对啊，我烧了你的房子 你这个小贱人
Edie!
Why would you do that?!
你为什么这么做？！
Can you blame me,after sending me that acid letter?
你写了那样的信 还能怪我吗？
Letter? What letter?
信？什么信？
From one where you admitted to stabbing me in the back by sleeping with karl.
那封你承认暗箭伤人 和Karl上床的信
You weren't supposed to get that.
你不应该收到那信的
I stole that back from the mailman.
我从邮递员那里偷回来了
So you were trying to hide the truth from me?
哦，你想瞒着我
This is not what we should focus on right now.The point is,
这个不是重点，重点是
you maliciously set fire to my house.
你故意在我们家放了火
Look, I admit I might have...overreacted a tad.
我承认我有可能，玩得有点过头
A tad?Edie, I have no roof!
有点过头？ Edie，我都无家可归了
You can't just go around burning down people's homes.
你怎么能随便就烧了人家的房子
Why not?You burnt down my home.
为什么不行 你烧了我的房子
You stole mike from me.You slept with my fianc?
你抢走了Mike 你和我未婚夫上床
That's the trifecta.
你就这样一而再再而三
You're lucky I didn't torch your car.
我没有烧掉你的车 已经够可以了
That's it.
够了
I'm going to the police, and I'm telling them what you did.
我要去报警 告诉他们你都做了些什么
Did what?I didn't do anything.
做了什么？ 我什么都没做
What? You just confessed.
你说什么？你刚刚承认
No, I didn't.
我没有啊
Did anyone else hear me confess?
有人听到了吗？
hello?Hello?
有人吗？有人吗？
no witnesses.
没有人证
No evidence, no confession.
没有物证，没有坦白
I guess we're done here.
我们说完了吧
You can go home now.
你可以回家了
Oh, wait. That's right.
哦，等等，对了
You don't have one.
你没有家了
no, no, xiao-mei,I've told you a million times. No red meat for mr. Solis.
不，不，小梅，我告诉你很多次了 不要给Solis先生吃牛羊肉
My triglycerides are through the roof.
我的脂肪含量太高了
Sweetie,I need some more cream.
亲爱的，我还有奶油
Xiao-mei, what's wrong?
小梅，怎么了？
She smell.
她有味道
Who smells? Gaby?
谁有味道？Gaby吗？
excuse me. What?
不好意思，你说什么？
Her perfume...make me sick.
她的香水，让我想吐
Honey, it's 100 bucks an ounce.
亲爱的，这香水一盎司就要100块
That tends to make everyone a little nauseous.
可能让人恶心吗？
Xiao-mei, your boobs--are they tender?
小梅，你的胸部是不是比平时软？
Carlos! Her boobs are none of your business.
Carlos！她的胸与你何干？
Gaby, think. She's sensitive to smell, nauseous and has swollen breasts.
Gaby，想想。她对气味敏感 恶心，胸部开始发涨
well, I just ran her blood work.
我刚刚做完她的血检
It looks like the insemination was successful.
看上去，授精成功了
Oh!Oh, my god.
天哪！天哪！
We're gonna have a baby!
我们要有孩子了
Now, you should know, since she's experiencing early symptoms,
你们要知道 她这么早就出现了症状
this might be a tough pregnancy for her.
可能怀孕过程会很辛苦
Not a problem. We are gonna treat her like a queen!
没关系，我们会把她当成皇后一样的！
Absolutely. You have nothing to worry about here.
那是，你不用担心
oh, mrs. Solis,you smell.
哦，Solis夫人，你有味道
Oh, yeah. Okay. Sorry.
哦，对，不好意思
I think it's gonna be a kick having susan and julie stay with us.
我觉得让Susan和Julie和我们一起住 简直好极了
It'll be like living in a sorority.We'll stay up late and we'll gossip and make s'mores.
就像女生联谊会一样 我们很晚才睡，随便聊天讲八卦
Doesn't that sound like fun?
很好玩吧
Why are you pretending to be happy?
你为什么装出一副开心的样子？
I heard you walking around your room all night long...crying.
我听到你在房间里走来走去... 你在哭
I don't want to talk about it.
我不想说这事
Look, I know why you're worried,but
我知道你担心，但是
andrew can take care of himself,
Andrew能照顾好自己的
and if he can't he shouldn't have run away in the first place.
如果他不能 一开始也不会离家出走
You know what? Maybe andrew leaving will be good for us.
你知道吗？ Andrew离开对我们来说可能是件好事
You are all I have left, and I am gonna be the best mother that I can be.
你现在是我的唯一 我会是最好的妈妈
There's definitely room for improvement.
确实还有很大的提高空间
It's just...
只是...
you kinda forgot my birthday.
你忘了我的生日
What?
什么？
Yeah. It was six weeks ago.
对，过了六个星期了
Oh, my god, danielle.I am so sorry.
天哪，Danielle，太抱歉了
It's okay.You had a lot going on.
没关系，你最近经历了太多事情
I mean,andrew was suing you, and you were pretty wasted that month.
Andrew告了你，你那段时间很颓废
Honey, you've gotta let me make it up to you.
亲爱的，你一定让我补偿你
I-I'm gonna throw you a birthday party with all your friends, okay?
我，我要给你开个生日会 邀请你所有的朋友，好吗？
That could be cool.
不错
You know what else I'd like?
你知道我还想要什么？
Name it. It's yours.
你说吧，都给你
I want andrew's room.
我想要Andrew的房间
You said he's probably not coming back, and I could really use the extra closet space.
你说他可能不会回来了 我想用他的衣橱
But, sweetheart, this is--this is his room.
但是，亲爱的，那是他的房间
Mom, you forgot my birthday.
妈，你忘了我的生日
You're really in no position to negotiate.
你没权利讨价还价
Honey, where am I gonna putall of his things?
亲爱的，我该把他的东西放在哪呢？
And, you know, he might come back at some point.
他可能以后会回来
He won'T.Like you said,I'm all you have left.
他不会的，像你说的一样 我是你的仅有的了
Atlantic city?
大西洋城？
Yeah, it's last minute, but jerry got a great deal ona suite at one of the casinos,
嗯，临时通知的 不过Jerry在一个赌场订了一间大套房
and a bunch of the old gang is coming in from new york,
一群老朋友也要从纽约过来
and god, it's been foreversince I have been, so how could I turn that down?
我们好久都没有见了，怎么能拒绝
Yeah, how, indeed?
对啊，怎么能呢
What?
什么？
I didn't say anything.
我什么也没说
No, but you have that look.
对，但是你表情不对
Is something wrong?
- 有事吗？
-No!
没有！
except that I know you've been to atlantic city three times
只是我知道你上个月已经
in the last month without telling me.
去了三次大西洋城 但没有告诉我
Ed found the receipts when he did the office audit.
Ed在做审计的时候找到了发票
Other than that, no, nothing's wrong.
除了这些事情，没问题了
tom, it would be better for your general well-being
Tom,你要想过得太平点
if you did not laughat this moment in time.
刚才就不应该笑
Am I gonna have to ruin the surprise? Becauseit's a really good surprise.
非要我破坏这个惊喜吗？ 这可是个大大的惊喜哦
I'm thinking, yeah, ruin it.
我觉得，还是破坏它吧
I have been going to atlantic city for business.
我去亚特兰大是为了公事
I am up for a top spotwith jerry's firm, huffington promotions.
我要去Jerry的公司的高峰做会议 Huffington的促销项目
And if you don't believe me...
如果你不相信我...
you can call the C.E.O. Himself.
你可以给他们的CEO打电话
I am... so happy and I'm so relieved.
我总算是放心了
Did you think I was cheating?
你觉得我有外遇了?
- No! Absolutely not.
- 不! 完全没有
Lynette...
no! Okay, a little bit.
不! 好吧 有一点点
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
对不起 对不起
Ed found receipts for flowers and theater tickets. I mean, by the way, did you--
Ed发现了买花和戏票的收据 所以 你...
jerry and I went to a show, and the flowers were for milt's wife.
Jerry 和我一起去看的演出 而花是买给Milt太太的
I knew that. You didn'thave to tell me that. Why did you buy flowers for milt's wife?
啊 这个我知道 你不用告诉我这些 那你为什么要买花给Milt太太呢?
Lynette...
sorry. Stop. Done talking.That's fantastic.
对不起 好吧 不说了 这些太让人吃惊了
I love you !
我爱你!
我也爱你
carlos...
Carlos...
what's going on?
你在做什么?
Xiao-mei is feeling under the weather, so I took up the vacuuming.
小梅有点不舒服 所以就由我来吸尘
Oh, well,I'm sorry to hear that.
哦 你辛苦了
So, uh, did you move my beauty products? They're not in the bathroom.
恩 你是不是动了我的化妆品? 我在盥洗室没找到它们
Why in the hell?
怎么在客厅里?
I forgot to tell you.
我忘记告诉你了
Uh, youcan't use that stuff anymore.
你不能再用那些东西了
It really triggers xiao-mei's morning sickness.
它们总是引起小梅晨吐
All of it?Even my hair pomade?
所有这些? 连我的润发油也是?
Gives me stomachache.
它让我胃痛
Yeah, well,it gives me volume, so I guess we're both gonna have a problem.
哈，我需要发油来整头发 我想现在我们都有麻烦了
Do you have to be so high-maintenance?
你有必要这样保养吗?
You're not a model, carlos. Maintenance is my only skill.
你不是模特，Carlos 保养是我唯一的法宝
Please, no fight.
拜托 别吵了
If mrs. Solis smell bad,I be okay.
如果只是Solis太太闻起来让人不舒服 我没关系的
fine. I'll learn to live without product.
好吧 我争取不用它们
But when my hairstarts smelling like hair, I don't wanna hear a word.
到时候我头发难闻的时候 你可别埋怨
Surprise!
惊喜吧!
What the hell is that?
这是怎么了?
Isn't it darling?
怎么样 亲爱的?
I made it for your party.
这些都是给的生日派对用的
It's a big "1"and a big "7"...for "17."
这里一个大大的1和7 加起来就是17了
Were you up all night making that thing?
你为了做这些通宵了?
Yeah. I just wasn't tired. Oh, I wanna show you what else I've planned.
对啊 我一点都觉得累呢 对了 我再让你看看我还准备了些什么
I think you're gonna love it.
我想你一定会喜欢的
You got a fajita barand a juggler?
你准备了墨西哥料理 还打算请变戏法来?
No, relax.He's a very hip juggler.
你放心 他很会变戏法
He only performs to beatles songs,and I saw the video, and it's absolutely thrilling.
他只来唱唱披头士的歌 我看过他的表演录象 真的很不错
Mom, I don't want any of this stuff. It's not even my real birthday.
妈妈 这些都不是我想要的 而且我生日已经过了
Danielle, I just want you to have the best party you have ever had in your entire life.
Danielle 我只是想让你享有一个 你生命中最好的生日派对
I just want a few friends to come over and hang out.
我只是想邀请一些朋友聚聚 一起出去玩
You can make a cake,but giant balloon numbers?
你可以做个蛋糕 但是有必要用这么夸张的气球数字?
I mean, come on.They would all make fun of me.
嗯 他们一定会嘲笑我的
Oh.
哦
Okay.
好吧
Is that really necessary?
有必要这样吗?
Honey, I can't possibly put it in the garbage as is.
亲爱的 我实在不能就这样把它们当垃圾扔掉
It's just another morning with the van de kamps.
她一向是这样的
Oh, susan,did I wake you?
哦 Susan 吵醒你了吗?
Uh, no. No, I was up.
哦 不不 我已经醒了
Well,I'm sorry about the noise.
恩 抱歉弄出这么多噪音
It's just that danielle doesn't want balloons, and I'm kind of pressed for time.
Danielle不想要气球 所以我要尽快把它们弄掉
Bree... are you okay?
Bree... 你还好吧?
She said she doesn't want balloons.
她说她不想要这些气球
I'm fine.
我很好啊
mom?
妈?
Look, I know you're out there. Please, just talk to me.
我知道你在外面 拜托 跟我说句话
Mom, I need something to drink.Just some water, some juice.Something, anything. Please.
妈 我要喝水 就一些水 一些果汁 给我点东西 任何东西都好
Mom!
妈!
You want me to say that I set caleb up?
你是想听我说我陷害了Caleb?
Yeah, I did it.
对 是我做的
I started thinking about all those years--
这些年来我一直都在想
years that we had to take care of him, and...
想起我们这些年总是不停的在照顾他...
I just thought maybe once he was gone,
我只是想如果他不在了
we could have a normal life.
我们就可以过正常的生活了
and I'm sorry.
对不起
But, mom, you have gotto let me out of here now.
但是 妈妈 你必须现在让我出去
Damn you!
混蛋！
You were willing to stand by and let me murder your brother without reason.
你就站在边上看着我毫无原因的杀了你哥哥
That's an unforgivable betrayal.
这绝对不可原谅
I am so consumed with rage.
我快被愤怒吞噬了
It's best you stay in there,because if I let you out, I don't know what I might do to you.
你最好是待在里面 如果我让你出来 我不确定会对你做出什么
hello?
喂?
I need edie to spillher guts.
我要Edie自己把她干的好事都说出来
What do you know about wearing a wire?
你知道怎么用录音机吗?
So you see the little red light?
你看到那个小小的红灯吗?
It's all voice-activated,so if the light's on, you're recording.
是声控的 就是说只要灯亮着的 你就录上了
Uh, let me show you how to tape it on.
恩 让我教你怎么把它粘在身上
Oh, okay.
嗯 好
Sorry if my hands are cold.
不好意思 我手有点凉
Um... no, that's okay.They're fine.
嗯... 不 还好 还好
So you sure you wanna do this?
你确定你要怎么做了?
Yeah. I'm sort of up against the wall.
恩 我到处碰壁
The insurance company needs proof fast,
保险公司说要尽快找到证据
and things are sort of weirdat bree'S. I don't wanna over stay my welcome.
而且住在Bree家让我觉得有点怪怪的 我不想在那边长住
Well, if things get tough,you can always stay here.
如果实在不行 你可以住在我这里的
Testing, testing.
喂喂
I'm sorry. Did you just invite me to move in with you?
等下 你刚刚是在邀请我搬进来和你一起住吗?
Well, you and julie in the spare bedroom.
你和Julie可以住在空着的那间卧室
You've...
你...
you've been saying how you want to be friends again,
你说可以重新做朋友的
and you're right.
你是对的
There's no reason we can't be friends.
我们的确没有不能重新做朋友的理由
You sure that won't put a crimpin your, uh, dating life?
你确定这不会影响你的...感情生活?
You know, that girl you were at the movies with?
就是那个和你一起去看电影的女孩?
No. That was a one-time thing.
不 就约会过一次
But what about that guy,though? Orson.
那Orson呢?
Yeah, he just heard about the fire and came over to help.We're friends.
他听说了房子着火的事 也过来帮了帮忙 我们只是朋友
Oh. So... neither of us is dating anybody.
哦 所以...我们都没有和别人在一起
Guess not.
我想是这样的
I got my boarding pass.
我已经换了登机牌了
Do what you need to do and don't worry about the kids. I'll keep 'em out of trouble.
去做你想做的 不用担心这些孩子 我会好好照顾他们的
Is this crazy?
这会不会太疯狂了?
Following tom across the country just to spy on him?
费尽心机跟踪Tom就为了暗中监视他?
If he knewI was doing this...
如果他知道我这么做...
god, I don't thinkI can go through with this.
天啊 我都不相信他会原谅我
Now, look, there's probably nothing going on,
等等 其实他可能真的没有骗你
but you need to know the truth.
但是你要知道真相到底如何
Do I? I'm happy.I mean, I was.
真的要吗? 我过的很好 我是说 我以前过的很好
Why don't I just look the other way and pretend nothing's wrong? Lots of women can do that.
为什么我不能从另个角度想想 然后装成什么都没有发生 很多女人不都这样吗
But we both know you're not one of them.
但是我们都知道你不会是她们其中的一员
And what if I see him with another woman?
那如果我看到他和别的女人在一起呢?
What then?
我要怎么办?
I own a gun.
我有把枪
you okay here?
你还好吗?
I'm fine. Why?
很好, 怎么了?
It's just, people have been asking about the cake,and you've been
大家都在问蛋糕的事情, 而你已经
icing it for over an hour.
上奶油上了一个小时了
Well,I just keep messing it up. I don't know what's wrong with me.
我只是一直做不好 不知道怎么搞得
You're probably just tired.
你大概是累了
My mom and I heard you up all night.
我妈和我知道你一晚没睡
it just keeps coming out too thick.
总是挤得太厚
You know,people aren't gonna care if the icing isn't perfect.
大家不会在意蛋糕奶油太厚的
People care about details.
大家在意细节
Someday when danielle looks back, I want her to remember
当danielle回忆起来, 我希望她记得
just how perfect her cake looked and how hard her mother worked to make her happy.
她的蛋糕是多么的完美 她妈妈为了让她高兴是多么的努力
This cake is a symbol of my love.
这个蛋糕代表着我的爱
Well, it looks delicious.
它看起来很美味
happy birthday to you
祝你生日快乐
happy birthday dear danielle
生日快乐, 亲爱的danielle
stop!One of the candles went out.
停! 有一支蜡烛灭了
Um, we're gonna have to do this all over again. I'm sorry. I'll be right back.
我们得重新来一次 不好意思, 我马上回来
Mom, it's all right.
妈妈, 这没有关系
Sweetheart,this is your special day. All of your candless hould be lit.
亲爱的, 这是你特别的日子 所有的蜡烛都应该亮着
It'll just take me two seconds.
马上就好
Is she serious?
她是认真的?
Welcometo my own private hell.
欢迎来到我的私人地狱
That is some serious frosting.
那是些“认真”的糖霜
all righty.
好了
who touched this?
谁碰的?
Mom, what is the matter? It's just a little frosting.
妈妈, 有什么关系? 只是一点糖霜
Somebody ruined your cake,and I wanna know who could be that thoughtless.
有人毁了你的蛋糕 我想知道是谁那么不小心
Was it you? Or you?!Who was it?
是你吗? 或者是你?! 是谁?
Mom, please,you're embarrassing me.
妈妈, 拜托, 你在让我尴尬
You. You look like a girlwho enjoys her frosting.
你, 你看起来像是个爱糖霜的女孩
No! No, I didn't touch it.
不! 我没有动它
It's just a cake, for god sakes. Will you please just cut it?
只是个蛋糕 你能不能把它切了完事？
Mrs. Van de kamp--
Van de kamp太太--
open your mouth.I wanna smell your breath.
张开嘴, 我要闻闻
It wasn't me!It was barbie.
不是我! 是barbie
Barbie!
what the hell is wrong with you?!
你哪里不对劲吗?!
Now it's ruined!Everything is ruined!
现在它毁了! 所有事情都毁了
you can just...leave that there, and I'll, um...clean it up later.
你们可以不管它, 我稍候会清理的
Xiao-mei, what are you doing in our bed?
小梅, 你在我们的床上干什么?
I said she could sleepin there from now on.
我让她以后睡那儿
It's got the bathroom,
这里有洗手间,
you know, in case she gets sick in the middle of the night.
以防她半夜作呕
Well, what's wrong with the guest bathroom?
客人用的洗手间不能用吗?
It's too far away.
太远了
It's right down the hall.
就在大厅那儿
Gaby, she needs her rest.
Gaby,她需要休息
And besides, that bed is much more comfortable than the one in the guest room.
而且, 这张床比客房那张舒服多了
Yeah, I know.That's why I had the movers put it in here, where we sleep.
我知道, 所以我让人搬到这里 ——我们睡觉的地方
Maybe I go to my bed.
我去我床上睡吧
Yes, xiao-mei,that would be good.
好的, 小梅, 这样很好
Fine.You can use our toilet.
好吧, 你可以用我们的厕所
ow! Stop kicking me.
别再踢我了
I'm just tryingto get comfortable.
我只想舒服点
Yeah, in a twin?Good luck.
是的, 在这张床上? 祝你好运
God, I want my bed back.
我想要回我的床
We'll go buy a nice big onetomorrow and put it in here, okay?
明天去买一张大床放在这里, 行了吧？
That is not the point.
不是这个问题
We area week into this pregnancy, and you're already putting xiao-mei's needs before mine.
怀孕才刚开始 你已经把小梅的需要放在我的前面
Well, she's the priority now. She's the mother of my child.
她现在是首要的, 她是我孩子的母亲
Like hell she is.That is my egg.
她是就见鬼了, 那是我的卵子
You know what I mean.She's the...
你知道我是什么意思, 她是...
oven, carlos. The oven. A well-cared-for,well-paid oven.
烤箱, carlos 被精心呵护 而且拿着高工资的烤箱
It came out wrong.I'm sorry, okay? Now can we justget some sleep?
我说错了好吗? 我们能睡了吗?
Babe, I'm sorry.I swear.I swear I didn't mean to. My leg just cramped up.
亲爱的, 对不起, 我发誓 我不是故意的, 脚抽筋了
Where are you going? That's my pillow!
你去哪儿? 那是我的枕头
Good night.
晚安
matthew!
mom, come on.
妈妈, 别这样
Oh, my god.What are you doing in there?
天啊, 你在那里干什么？
Danielle, is that you?
Danielle, 是你吗？
My mom found out what we did to caleb. She flipped out and locked me in here.
我妈知道了我们对caleb做的事 她发怒了, 把我锁在这儿
Don't worry. I'll get you out.
别担心, 我会把你弄出来的
Be really careful, okay?Please, okay? I've never seen her like this before.
千万要小心, 好吗？我从来没见她这样
She's seriously lost it this time.
她真的是生气了
I know a little something about psycho moms. Trust me, I'll be fine.
我多多少少了解神经病妈妈 放心, 我会没事的
hey.
嗨
Cleaning up after the big party?
在打扫?
Yeah.
是的
You know, it's late.
现在很晚了
Why don't you, uh,go to bed and,
你何不, 呃, 去睡觉
you know,let julie and I help you with that in the morning?
等明天早晨让julie和我帮你打扫
Oh, that's okay.I can't sleep anyway.
没事, 反正我也睡不着
Are you... okay?
你还好吧？
I take it you heard what happened.
我猜你已经知道了
Yeah, when you flip out in front of the pep squad,word travels fast.
是啊, 你当着那群兴奋的孩子面前发脾气 消息传得很快
It was the oddest sensation.I was fine,
那真的是奇怪的感觉, 我之前好好的
and everything was fine,and then suddenly I was on the outside of my body
都是好好的, 突然我跳出我的身体
watching a woman who looked like me becoming a raving maniac.
看着一个长得和我一模一样的女人 变成一个发怒的疯子
Bree, I'm worried about you.Do...
Bree, 我很担心你
do you think that you should see someone?
你是不是应该...去看看医生？
Oh, no, I'm fine.I'm just tired, that's all.
不, 我很好 我只是有点累了, 没别的
I just need a long rest,and then I'm gonna beas good as new.
我需要一个长时间的休息 然后就没事了
Okay, well, then why don't you stop and go to bed?
那好吧, 那你为什么不停下来上床睡觉？
Because, um, I can't sleep just yet.
因为, 我暂时还睡不着
Why not?
为什么?
Because when I sleep,I dream,
因为我一睡着就做梦
and when I dream,I keep seeing andrew's face in that rearview mirror.
我一做梦就看见andrew 在车子倒后镜里的样子
Okay, what are you talking about?
你在说什么?
Andrew, didn't run away.
Andrew, 没有跑掉
I, dropped him off in the middle of nowhere,
我把他扔在了荒郊野外
told him that I couldn'tbe around him anymore, and then...
告诉他我不能再和在一起, 然后-
I drove off.
我开车走了
So I just need a little time to forget what I've done, and then I can sleep again.
我需要一点时间去忘记我的所作所为 然后我就能睡着了
Hey.
哎
You know,I am not even tired.
我也不累
So... why don't I stay up and help you?
所以...何不我也不睡觉 帮你一起清扫？
That would be nice.
那样太好了
hello?
喂?
Hey, you.How you doing?
喂, 你还好吗?
Hey! Great.
嗨! 我很好
Great. How's atlantic city?Are you, um, winning some money?
很好, 亚特兰大怎样? 你赢钱了吗?
Oh, I'm about even.
不输不赢
Actually, I'm heading backinto the casino right now to try my luck again.
事实上, 我现在正准备再去赌场试试运气
Yeah?You're quite a gambler.
是吗？你真是个赌博者
where's jerry?
jerry在哪儿?
Uh, jerry?He--he's right here. Hey, honey, how are the kids?
呃, jerry?他--他就在这儿 亲爱的, 孩子们还好吗?
Great. Great.They're in the day care room.
很好, 很好, 他们在日托室呢
I'M... looking at 'em right now.
我现在正在看着他们
hey, why don't youwalk in there and, put 'em on the phone with meso I can say hi?
你何不现在走过去 让我和他们问声好?
Okay. Sure.
好啊, 当然
First,can I talk to jerry?
首先, 我能和jerry聊几句吗？
Why do you wanna talk to jerry?
你为什么想和jerry说话?
Well, just, you know, say hello. It's been a long time.
只是, 想问声好, 那么久没见了
wow, man, that is weird.
哦, 好奇怪啊
Can you hear--do you hear that car alarm?
你能听到--你听到报警器吗?
Uh... no.
没有
It's strange,because I can hear it here and through the phone.
好奇怪, 我同时在这里和电话里听到
Whoa. That's weird kind of feed back, you know?
哦, 那是一种奇怪的回响, 你知道吗？
physics can be spookythat way. Listen, I gotta go.I gotta go.
有些物理现象是很怪异的 听着, 我得走了, 我得走了
Ed is talking to me,and, um, I'll call you back later?
Ed在和我说话, 我迟点再打给你?
Um, okay.
好的
Okay, bye.
好的, 再见
Bye, honey.
再见, 亲爱的
9-1-1.Is this an emergency?
9-1-1 有紧急事件吗？
I think so.
是的
My neighbor, paul young,has been threatening me.
我的邻居, paul young, 一直在威胁我
Is he there right now?
他现在在那儿吗?
No.
没有
Ma'am, until he actuallydoes something, there's nothingwe can do.
女士, 除非他做出行动 否则我们无能为力
Well, I won't live in fear anymore.
我再也不能在恐惧中生活了
If you people refuse to confront him,
如果你们拒绝去找他
I guess I'll just have to do it myself.
我不得不自己解决
no, edie, wait.
不要, edie, 等一下
Um, I don't wanna fight.
我不想争执
I know that we've had our differences, but, you know, we hada friendship going there,
我知道我们有很多不同 但是, 我们的友谊还是在那儿的
and I just think we owe itto ourselves to talk about what happened.
我觉得我们应该谈谈发生了的事
What's there to talk about?It happened.
还有什么好谈的? 已经发生了
I walked down to your house...
我走到你房子
I had a watering can...
拿了一个喷水壶
what?
什么?
filled it with gasoline and...
把它装满了汽油, 然后
boom!Laughed my ass off.
砰！
Okay, wait.Could you just swallow?
好的, 等等, 你能先咽完东西吗？
'Cause I couldn't really...what you were saying--
因为我不能听见你在说什么
and that was basically it.
基本上就是那样了
One of the best days of my life.
我生命中最完美的日子之一
Well, see, you were chewing, and so I didn't really hear what you said.
你在咀嚼, 所以我听不清你在讲什么
Could you just say it again?
你能不能再说一遍
I burnt your house down.It was great. What do you want?
我把你房子烧了, 那太棒了, 你想怎样？
So, uh, y-you then a-admit
那就是, 唔, 你承认了
burning down my house on purpose?
你是故意烧掉我房子的?
You're wearing a wire,aren't you?
你带了录音机是吧?
Huh?
啊?
Open that blouse.
- 打开你的衣服
What?
什么?
Open that blouse!
打开你的衣服
you can't out run me, mayer! I'm in the best shape of my life!
你跑不过我的,  mayer! 我现在状态奇佳
Well, good, then you'll be prime meat picking when you go to jail!
那太好了, 入狱以后你会是抢手货了
You give it!
交出来!
bite me!
来追我啊!
No! No!
不! 不!
what the hell? Huh.
搞什么鬼?
Nine months of long nights on the couch loomed before gabrielle...
在沙发上睡九个月—— 这种阴影笼罩着gabrielle
and she had decided she would not take it lying down.
她决定不能逆来顺受
So she dipped into her supply of forbidden perfumes...
她把被禁的各种香水找了出来
determined that in this battle...
在这场的战斗中她充满自信
she would be the one to come out smelling like a rose.
一定会是那个满载花香的胜者
I think I take nap now.
我现在想睡睡午觉
Yeah, sure,knock yourself out.
当然, 请自便
Aah!
嗷!
honey?
亲爱的?
Boys?
孩子们?
Anybody home?
有人在家吗?
Hey, mrs. Mccluskey,excuse me. You haven't see nlynette around, have you?
嗨, Mccluskey夫人, 打扰一下 你有见到lynette吗?
She's not home. She's not answering her cell phone.
她不在家, 也不接手机
She packed up the kids and the puppy and left.
她把孩子和小狗一起带走了
Packed 'em up? Why?
带走他们? 为什么?
She followed you to atlantic city. She knows about your other woman.
她跟踪你到了大西洋城 她知道你和另外一个女人的事情
Boy, you're just lucky you're not my husband.
孩子, 你不是我丈夫实在太幸运了
Hi.
嗨!
okay, first, let me say, I'm really sorry about the yellow jackets.
首先我要说, 很遗憾你被黄蜂叮了
And... also, no matter how mad I am about what you did,
还有, 无论我对你做的事情多么生气
I don't want to see you go to prison.
我不想见你去监狱
So I came with a solution.
所以, 我有一个解决的办法
Why don't you just come forward and tell the police that
你何不去告诉警察
you saw some vagrant lurking by my garage with a can of gasoline?
你见到一些拿着汽油的游民 在我车房附近游荡？
And if you do that,then I'll destroy the tape.
如果你这样做, 我就毁了磁带
And then the insurance company will pay the claim. Nobody gets hurt.
然后保险公司会赔偿, 没人受到伤害
Does that sound good?
你说怎么样?
come closer.
靠近点
take your stinking deal and shove it.
想也别想你这恶心的交易
Edie...
Edie
every time something bad happens to me, you're standing nearby.
每一次坏事发生在我头上, 你都站在附近
Well, I've had it.No more pretending to be friends.When I get outta here,
我受够了, 别再假装朋友 我出院以后-
I'm gonna destroy you.
我会毁掉你
Okay, I'm just gonna think that this is the meds talking,
好吧, 我会把这当成药物作用
and I'll come back tomorrow.
我明天会再来的
Don't bother.
别白费力气了
Okay, edie,I'm in trouble here.
好了,  edie, 我这儿有麻烦
Oh, I'm sure you'll turn on the waterworks, and the whole neighborhood will come running.
是的, 我肯定你会打开你的眼泪闸门 整个社区的人都会同情你
That's not true.
他们总这样  不是这样的
Sure, it is.
就是这样
You never miss an opportunity to play the victim,
你从来不会浪费一个扮演受害者的机会
and you think just because everybody always comes to your rescue,
你以为人们总是会来拯救你
it means that you're loved.
是因为你招人喜爱
Well, it doesn't.
不是的
It means that you're helpless.
这只说明你没用
Now get out.
滚出去
Just get out.
滚吧
Hey there.
嗨
Hi.
So you given any thought to staying at my place?
你有没有考虑来我这里暂住?
Oh, yeah, that. Um...
哦, 是的, 这件事, 呃...
look, I really appreciatethe offer, but I think I'm gonna have to pass.
我很感激你的帮助, 但我不能接受
- Really?
- 真的吗?
Yeah.
是的
I think it's best.
我认为这样最好
I don't wanna get a rep around here for being a charity case,you know?
我不想成为一个被施舍的对象, 你知道吗？
Well, I didn't mean it that way just one friend helping out another.
没有这个意思--只是朋友间互相帮忙
I know, but I can figure this out on my own.
我知道, 但我自己能解决
At least I'm gonna try.
至少我要去试一下
You know, I'm stronger than people give me credit for.
我比人们想象的要坚强
I really am.
真的
Well, if there's anything I can do...
如果有什么我可以做的
you know what would be nice?
你知道怎样做比较好吗?
Why don't you just stop over for coffee sometime?
你时不时过来喝喝咖啡怎样？
Okay.
好的
I mean, that is after I get running water and electricity again...
我的意思是, 等我有了自来水和电之后
and a coffeemaker.
还有一个煮咖啡机
I hope you're happy.That poor girl
这下你开心了, 那可怜的女孩
can hardly even come upstairs now because of you.
现在连楼都不敢上
Carlos, stop with the dance. It's already in the wallpaper.
Carlos, 别跳舞了, 香气已经渗入墙纸了
Now I swear, if anything happens to that kid because of you...
我发誓, 如果由于你的所作所为 宝宝有什么事
oh, it's perfume,not toxic gas.
只是香水, 又不是有毒气体
Why are you acting this way?
为什么你要这样做?
Because I seethe writing on the wall, and it scares the hell out of me.
因为我看见了墙上的“字” 我很害怕
Meaning what?
什么意思?
From the second xiao-mei got pregnant, you have found a million
当小梅怀孕的那一刻起 你找到了一千零一个理由
and oneways to tell me that that baby is more important to you than me.
告诉我那个宝宝对你来说比我重要的多
Oh, come on, gaby.
别这样, gaby
No! Men can't help it.When they become fathers, they become lousy husbands,
不! 男人们都情不自禁 当父亲以后就变成糟糕的丈夫
and some wives don't mind,but you didn't marry one of those women.
有些妻子不在乎, 但你娶的这个不是
I don't think I can sleepin here tonight.
今晚我不能睡这里
The air's just a little too toxic.
空气有点太毒了
she kick you out, too?
她把你也赶出来了?
Marriage is complicated,xiao-mei. You'll find that out someday.
婚姻是复杂的, 小梅 你总有一天会知道的
You feel like watching some trashy american tv?
你想看一出垃圾美剧吗?
I make you sandwich.Roast beef.
我为你做了三文治烤牛肉的
oh, man.Gaby's got meon this health kick thing. She'll kill meif I eat red meat.
天啊, Gaby最讨厌这种垃圾食品了 如果我吃了红肉 她会杀了我
I will not tell.
我不会告诉她
Taste good?
好吃吗?
Real good.
好吃
Matthew, wake up.I have your breakfast.
Matthew, 起来吃早餐
I might be furious with you, but never let it be saidthat I'm cruel.
我对你非常愤怒, 但不代表我对你残忍
I advise you not to charge this door, because I am not in the mood for any unpleasantness.
我建议你不要冲门 因为我没心情碰到不愉快的事情
Matthew?Matthew?
jeez, danielle! I thought you were just gonna steal the key.
天啊,  danielle! 我以为你只是偷钥匙
Let's just get out of here.
我们快逃吧
mother, matthew and i  are running away together, and we're never coming back.
妈妈, matthew和我一起离开了 我们再也不回来了
If you want me to be happy, you won't try to find us.
如果你想让我快乐, 不要试图找我们
Living in that house with you was like being in a prison.
在那所房子里与你一起生活 就像在监狱里一样
You drove me to do this, so i hope you'll blame yourself.
你逼我这样做的, 所以要怪就怪你自己
Have a nice life. Danielle.
祝你生活愉快 Danielle
Hello.
你好
My name is bree van de kamp, and I'd like to admit myself for psychiatric observation.
我叫bree van de kamp 我需要入院接受精神病监护
All right,what seems to be the problem?
好的, 有什么问题?
I think I'm about to have a nervous breakdown.
我认为我将要精神崩溃了
Damn it!
该死!
what the hell?
搞什么鬼?
That psychotic bitch.
那个精神病婊子
there was no confrontation.
根本没有冲突
Felicia tillman's the one who made the call. She's the anonymous tip.
是Felicia tillman打得电话 她是那个匿名报信者
Let's just go over there right now.
我们现在马上去那里
I guarantee you,the woman is having a cocktail, laughing her ass off.
我保证, 那个女人 正在喝一杯鸡尾酒, 心中狂喜
We're not going anywhere yet, sir.
我们暂时不能去任何地方, 先生
yes, I know there's blood everywhere.
是的, 我知道这里到处都是血迹
She probably got it from a pig so she can vandalize everything I own.
也许是猪血, 她想夺走我所有的一切
Sergeant...
警长
what is it?
什么东西?
Put your hands where I can see 'em.
手放在我能看见的地方
Oh, man, she's good.
哦天, 她真行
It's a shocking moment for each of us,
对我们每一个人来说 这都非常震惊的时刻
that moment we realize we are all alone in this world.
令我们意识到, 我们在这世上是寂寞的
The family we take for granted could one day abandon us.
我们认为理所当然的家人 会突然遗弃我们
The husband we trust so implicitly might betray us...
我们那么深信的丈夫也许会背叛我们
the daughter we love so deeply perhaps won't return to us.
我们深爱着的女儿 也许再也不会回到我们身边
And then we could end up all by ourselves.
我们也许只能孤独终老
Of course, some see great value in going it alone.
当然, 也有人喜欢孤身一人
For example...
例如...
sorry about the dust,mrs. Huber.
抱歉灰尘很大, Huber太太
We don't get too many tourists this far up the mountain.
这么高的山上, 并没有太多的游客
First snows come, and this placeis completely cut off.
第一场雪降临, 这里就彻底隔绝了
Dropping off the face of the earth now that's what I call a vacation.
让自己的面孔从地球上消失--这是我所谓的假期
I'm sorry.
抱歉
Sometimes I'm just all thumbs.
我这个人, 手比较笨
The Desperate Housewives Season 02  Episode 22
绝望的主妇 第2季 第22集
The End-
=完=-